whatuseek.com 2008-05-09

# whatUseek - Privacy Policy

|   
---  
| 

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

whatUseek respects your privacy.  The following details our information gathering and use practices for the following whatUseek sites: whatUseek.com, changeAlarm.com, and siteLevel.com.  You may click on a question link from the list below to be brought to a topic directly.

| 1. |  | [What information does whatUseek collect and how is it used?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#1)  
   
---|---|---  
2. |  | [What is whatUseek's policy on sending emails to its customers and visitors?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#2)  
   
3. |  | [With whom does whatUseek share information and for what purpose does it do so?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#3)  
   
4. |  | [What is whatUseek's Opt Out Policy?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#4)  
   
5. |  | [What will happen to my information if whatUseek, or a portion of, is acquired or is merged with another company?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#5)  
   
6. |  | [How are updated versions of this privacy policy presented?](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#6)  

1. |  | What information does whatUseek collect and how is it used?  
   
---|---|---  
  |  | 

whatUseek collects and uses the following types of information: cookies, IP addresses, browser type, access times, URLs, registration and billing information, and tags for whether or not an email has been viewed.  The collection and use of each of these is described below:  

| a. |  | Cookies are used to assign identification to your computer and to track the effectiveness of marketing campaigns for whatUseek offerings.  Information stored in cookies includes reference numbers, which can be queried internally by whatUseek and correlated with other data stored locally on whatUseek servers.  Such reference numbers can track the effectiveness of a particular marketing campaign, manage sessions, personalize content for you, analyze traffic patterns and visitor behavior within whatUseek web sites for purposes of marketing and user friendliness, or perform other functions.  Another form of information stored in cookies is login information as part of the optional "Remember Me" function found throughout the whatUseek sites.  When the "Remember Me" function is turned on, your username and password is automatically inserted into the given login form.  You may turn off the cookies feature of your web browser within its preference settings, but in doing so, you will limit some of the features available to you in the whatUseek sites.  
   
---|---|---  
b. |  | Your IP addresses may also be tracked for purposes of security, diagnosing technical problems, managing sessions, personalize content for you, analyzing traffic patterns and visitor behavior within whatUseek web sites (as it applies to marketing and user friendliness), and/or identifying and performing functions relating to your specific geographic location.  
   
c. |  | Browser types, access times, and referring URLs (URLs from which a whatUseek page was linked) are recorded.  Except as stated otherwise in this privacy policy, whatUseek does not provide this information to any third parties, except in aggregate form.  
   
d. |  | In order to sign-up for services or make requests, such as for sales inquiries or proposals, we may ask you to submit personal information.  This information may include, for example, for name and email address.  You may always choose not to provide us with such information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or properly answer your inquiries.  
   
e. |  | If you register for a paid service on a whatUseek site, you may be required to submit billing information.  We make our best efforts to protect your billing information through encryption, although we cannot guarantee complete security.  In order to complete a transaction, payment information may be processed by a third-party, such as a merchant bank.  
   
f. |  | We may also collect information through the use of "pixel tags" included in email messages that we send you.  Pixel tags are small, invisible images that are included in HTML emails.  When an email with a pixel tag is viewed (and this pixel tag is accessed from our servers), we are able to record information relating to the viewing of this tag.  Such information would include, but is not limited to, the date and time at which the message was viewed, the email address, and the IP address of the user.  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
2. |  | What is whatUseek's policy on sending emails to its customers and visitors?  
   
  |  | On occasion we will email you information that we think you will find useful, including information about new products and services.  We may also contact you to see if you are interested in participating in market research regarding whatUseek.  It is our policy to send these promotional emails only to those who give us permission to do so.  In every such email, we will also have instructions on how to unsubscribe (and avoid receiving any more such emails).  Please see our Opt Out Policy section below for more information.  whatUseek may also contact you, by email or otherwise, to respond to your customer service inquiries, verify registration/billing information, answer sales inquiries, send your password or other account information to you, or perform similar communications.  If at any time you feel that you have received an email from whatUseek that you did not request, please tell of your concerns, along with a copy of the email to [privacy@whatUseek.com](mailto:privacy@whatUseek.com).  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
3. |  | With whom does whatUseek share information and for what purpose does it do so?  
   
  |  | whatUseek may disclose your information to our business partners in order to provide you with the services that you have requested, or to companies that offer a co-branded version of one of the whatUseek sites and/or services.  If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data collection processes of one of our partners, please contact that partner directly.  whatUseek does not have control over and is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of our business partners.

  whatUseek may also disclose your personal information to a third-party if it is believed in good faith that it is required by law or the legal process, to protect the rights or property of whatUseek or others, to resolve complaints about such matters as unsolicited email, or as otherwise described in the privacy policy.

  whatUseek may share aggregate demographic information with our advertisers or information collection companies, but will not reveal any personally identifiable information in such cases.  
  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
4. |  | What is whatUseek's Opt Out Policy?  
   
  |  | Many of the services available on the whatUseek sites provide you with the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners.  In addition, in our email communications, we will have instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive additional emails from us.  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
5. |  | What will happen to my information if whatUseek, or a portion of, is acquired or is merged with another company?  
   
  |  | In such a scenario, customer information may be turned over to the acquiring company.  Though we will endeavor to have the acquiring company maintain this privacy policy, we cannot guarantee that this will be the case.  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
6. |  | How are updated versions of this privacy policy presented?  
   
  |  | This privacy policy may be revised as new features and/or services are added to whatUseek's sites.  The latest version of our privacy policy will be posted and will be linked to from the whatUseek's site(s).  
  |  |  

  [ 

[back to top](http://www.whatuseek.com/privacy.shtml#top) ]  
|  |
